Lesson 3-3. A day-t-remember. We have all experienced days when everything goes wrong.
第3-3课。日常记者。我们已经经历了一切出错的日子。
A day may begin well enough. But suddenly everything seems to get out of control.
一天的开始可能已经足够好。但是突然，一切似乎都失控了。
What invariably happens is that a great number of things choose to go wrong at precisely the same.
总是发生的事情是，许多事情选择在完全相同的情况下出错。
Moment. It is as if a single, unimportant event set up a chain of reactions.
片刻。好像一个不重要的事件建立了一系列反应。
Let us suppose that you are preparing a meal and keeping an eye on the baby at the same time.
让我们假设您正在准备一顿饭并同时关注婴儿。
prelude: n.   序幕，前奏, unforeseen: adj. 意料之外的, series: n.   系列, catastrophe: n.   大祸，灾难
The telephone rings and this marks the prelude to an unforeseen series of catastrophes.
电话响了，这标志着一系列不可预见的灾难的前奏。
While you are on the phone, the baby pulls the tablecloth off the table, smashing half your
当您打电话时，婴儿将桌布从桌子上拉出，砸碎了一半
crockery: n.   陶器，瓦器
best crockery and cutting himself in the process. You hang up hurriedly and attend to baby,
最好的陶器和在此过程中割伤自己。你急忙挂在婴儿身上，
crockery: n.   陶器，瓦器
crockery, etc. Meanwhile, the meal gets burnt as if this were not enough to reduce you to tears.
陶器等。同时，这顿饭被烧毁了，好像这还不足以减少您的眼泪。
Your husband arrives, unexpectedly bringing three guests to dinner. Things can go wrong on a big scale.
您的丈夫到达，出乎意料地带三名客人去吃晚饭。事情可能会大大出错。
suburb: n.   郊区
As a number of people recently discovered in Paramata, a suburb of Sydney during the rush hour
正如许多人最近在高峰时段在悉尼郊区帕拉马塔（Parramatta）发现的那样
collide: v.   猛撞
one evening two cars collided and both drivers began to argue. The woman immediately behind the two
一个晚上，两辆汽车碰撞，两辆驾驶员开始争论。那个女人紧随两者后面
learner: n.   初学者, panic: n.   惊慌，恐慌
cars happened to be a learner. She suddenly got into a panic and stopped her car. This made the
汽车恰好是学习者。她突然陷入恐慌，停了车。这使得
driver following her break hard. His wife was sitting beside him holding a large cake. As she was
驾驶员努力休息。他的妻子坐在他旁边拿着一个大蛋糕。就像她一样
windscreen: n.   （汽车的）挡风玻璃
thrown forward, the cake went right through the windscreen and landed on the road. Seeing a cake
向前扔了蛋糕，穿过挡风玻璃，降落在路上。看到蛋糕
flying through the air. A lorry driver who was drawing up alongside the car pulled up all of a
飞过空中。一名货车司机，他在汽车旁边开车，拉起了所有
sudden. The lorry was loaded with empty beer bottles and hundreds of them slid off the back of
突然。货车装满了空的啤酒瓶，其中数百个滑落在后面
the vehicle. And on to the road. This led to yet another angry argument. Meanwhile, the traffic
车辆。并上路。这导致了另一个愤怒的论点。同时，交通
piled up behind. It took the police nearly an hour to get the traffic on the move again.
堆积在后面。警察花了将近一个小时才能再次行动。
stray: adj. 迷失的，离群的
In the meantime, the lorry driver had to sweep up hundreds of broken bottles. Only two stray dogs
同时，卡车司机不得不扫除数百瓶破碎的瓶子。只有两只流浪狗
confusion: n.   混乱, greedily: adv. 贪婪地, devour: v.   狼吞虎咽地吃
benefited from all this confusion. For they greedily devoured what was left of the cake. It was
从所有这些混乱中受益。因为他们贪婪地吞噬了蛋糕的剩下的东西。是
just one of those days.
只是其中之一。